<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<index version="1" name="del-paso ReaScripts">
  <category name="MIDI Editor">
    <reapack name="AdvancedChordGun.lua" type="script" desc="Advanced ChordGun">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[
# Advanced ChordGun

An expanded chord composition tool for REAPER inspired by Pandabot's ChordGun.
50+ chord types, intelligent next-chord suggestions, trailing chord history,
and humanized arpeggiation for sketching out complex harmony fast.

## Features

- 50+ chord types: triads, 6ths, 7ths, 9ths, 11ths, 13ths, altered dominants
  (7b9, 7#9, 7alt, 7b5b9, 7#5#9), half-diminished, m(maj7), maj7#5, and extended
  jazz voicings up to 10 notes
- Full scrollable chord grid showing every chord type on every scale degree at
  once, organized by category
- Next-chord suggestion engine that lights up the grid in green/yellow/orange
  based on shared pitch classes and root movement quality
- Current chord highlight in gold so you always know where you are
- Trailing chord history showing your harmonic path through the grid (toggleable)
- Arpeggiate mode with adjustable delay (10-120ms)
- Round Robin humanize toggle for randomized per-note timing and velocity
- Per-degree key bindings - assign any chord type to each number key (1-7)
- 7 modes supported: Ionian, Dorian, Phrygian, Lydian, Mixolydian, Aeolian, Locrian
- Live MIDI preview through whatever instrument you have armed
- Insert mode drops chords directly into the active MIDI editor at the cursor
- Inversion control (-4 to +4)
- Dropdowns for root, scale, octave, and velocity
- Clickable note buttons for every note in the played chord
- All settings persist with the project

## Keyboard Shortcuts

- 1-7: Play assigned chord for that scale degree
- 0: Stop all notes
- A: Toggle arpeggiate
- Up/Down: Scroll grid
- Esc: Close

## Source

https://github.com/del-paso/AdvancedChordGun
        ]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/del-paso/AdvancedChordGun</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0" author="del-paso" time="2026-04-11T00:00:00Z">
        <changelog><![CDATA[Initial release.]]></changelog>
        <source main="main midi_editor">https://github.com/del-paso/AdvancedChordGun/raw/main/AdvancedChordGun.lua</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
  </category>
</index>
