<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<index version="1" name="del-paso ReaScripts">
  <category name="MIDI Editor">
    <reapack name="AdvancedChordGun.lua" type="script" desc="Advanced ChordGun">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[
# Advanced ChordGun

An expanded chord composition tool for REAPER inspired by Pandabot's ChordGun.
50+ chord types, intelligent next-chord suggestions, trailing chord history,
humanized arpeggiation, chord finder with piano, and drag-to-assign key bindings.

## Features

- 50+ chord types: triads, 6ths, 7ths, 9ths, 11ths, 13ths, altered dominants, and extended jazz voicings up to 10 notes
- Full scrollable chord grid showing every chord type on every scale degree at once, organized by category
- Next-chord suggestion engine that lights up the grid based on harmonic compatibility
- Current chord gold highlight and trailing chord history showing your harmonic path
- Arpeggiate mode with adjustable delay and Round Robin humanize for organic timing/velocity
- Per-degree key bindings with independent octave offset and inversion per degree
- Drag chords from the grid to degree slots to assign them to number keys
- 3-octave chord finder piano for identifying chords by clicking notes
- 7 modes: Ionian, Dorian, Phrygian, Lydian, Mixolydian, Aeolian, Locrian
- Adjustable text size (S/M/L/XL)
- Window size and position persist between sessions
- All settings persist with the project

## Keyboard Shortcuts

- 1-7: Play assigned chord for that scale degree
- 0: Stop all notes
- A: Toggle arpeggiate
- Up/Down: Scroll grid
- Esc: Close

## Source

https://github.com/del-paso/AdvancedChordGun
        ]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/del-paso/AdvancedChordGun</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="2.0" author="del-paso" time="2026-04-19T00:00:00Z">
        <changelog><![CDATA[
v2.0:
- Per-degree octave offset and inversion controls
- Drag-and-drop chord assignment from grid to degree slots
- 3-octave chord finder piano with individual key highlighting
- Adjustable text size (S/M/L/XL) with +/- controls
- Window size and position persist between sessions
- Trail/Arp toggle overlap bug fixed
- Clear button for chord finder redesigned as proper button
        ]]></changelog>
        <source main="main midi_editor">https://github.com/del-paso/AdvancedChordGun/raw/main/AdvancedChordGun.lua</source>
      </version>
      <version name="1.0" author="del-paso" time="2026-04-11T00:00:00Z">
        <changelog><![CDATA[Initial release.]]></changelog>
        <source main="main midi_editor">https://github.com/del-paso/AdvancedChordGun/raw/main/AdvancedChordGun.lua</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
  </category>
</index>
